<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Humanity Torbay</title>
    <description>Making a difference to people's lives.
</description>
    <link>https://elken.github.io/humanity-torbay//</link>
    <atom:link href="https://elken.github.io/humanity-torbay//feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2017 15:35:36 +0100</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2017 15:35:36 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.5.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Future plans</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;It’s been a busy day to day with many visitors. Lots of meetings and planning. We are open this Friday from 10-2 and as of next week we are open on a Saturday from 10-2. Can I say a big thank you to all our volunteers who are just the best. Wonderful to meet Clive from community larder really lovely man. Thank you councillor Mark King for the lovely visit myself and humanity look forward to many more from you. Fantastic to see the lovely Alan Millis bless you. Big thank you to Kerry for the £200 donation we really appreciate it. Big thank you to Melville gang we love ❤️ you at humanity you are all fabulous thank you for inviting me to talk. I can not tell you how thrilled we are with the fantastic donation for our homeless and vulnerable. Another person housed today we are all so happy with love and blessing and the will to succeed and make a difference to people’s lives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;❤️ to you all x&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>https://elken.github.io/humanity-torbay//future-plans/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://elken.github.io/humanity-torbay//future-plans/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Weekly update</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This week has been a busy one. We’ve had over 100 people come to see us with many different problems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most of these homeless/vulnerable people have been fed, watered and given excellent advice by our dedicated team of volunteers, and helpers, and numerous have been housed. We do this because we care and are thrilled to be helping so many people in our local community. None of us are paid and we are determined to make a difference. Every person counts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have also had a huge amount of clothes donated that will go to those who need them the most and they will help many people. Please keep them coming. We always need food to feed the increased amount of people though our doors. Financial donations are very much appreciated, all the bills we pay are entirely funded by these, and this is the best way you can help fund us directly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This week also saw up getting our website up and running. This will be updated daily, during the week, so keep an eye on it – www.humanitytorbay.org.uk&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can also find us on Twitter and Instagram as HumanityTorbay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please share these where ever you can. The more people who know about us the better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Big Love&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;XxX&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>https://elken.github.io/humanity-torbay//weekly-update/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://elken.github.io/humanity-torbay//weekly-update/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Another successful day</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Thank you for all the clothing donations we received today so much appreciated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today we had 43 in for help and support with 4 being housed.We have also been offered 10 jobs in paignton for our guys with a local firm, many thanks. At humanity we are non religious, we support every creed and this is why we are Humanity Torbay, every person counts no matter what. We would like to thank everyone who is helping us and we greatly appreciate all of your help. Housing is the way forward and jobs. Nobody should be on the streets and at humanity we are helping to stop that thank you to the 13 volunteers we had today&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With love ❤️ and hugs x&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>https://elken.github.io/humanity-torbay//another-successful-day/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://elken.github.io/humanity-torbay//another-successful-day/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Food donations</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We now need help with food for lunches so if people would like to donate food or money we would be grateful. Be assured that we are all volunteers and have no paid staff.
Please share and support your local homeless people.
Big love ❤️❤️&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>https://elken.github.io/humanity-torbay//food-donations/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://elken.github.io/humanity-torbay//food-donations/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Donate, don't dump</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/donate-dont-dump.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Donate, don't dump&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>https://elken.github.io/humanity-torbay//dont-dump/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://elken.github.io/humanity-torbay//dont-dump/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
